It's my birthday and for my birthday I want
what I have wanted for the last 38 years even
before I was able to verbalize it.
I want world peace an end to poverty solution
to the climate change crisis just the basics
like what all of us want and I think its obtainable
If you know me in real life I hope you know
me as someone who is both compassionate and
intelligent
I, unlike Trump, underestimate my ideas and
talents so I do not say this lightly.
This thing inside of me that is trying to
get out this idea is one that can save us
all.
I have spent the last year trying to explain
it to the masses and come to the conclusion
that I am just not that person.
I concentrate too much on the HOW we are going
to solve it instead of the WHY that speaks
to people and I have trouble conveying the
what i find it too complex
This video is an attempt to explain the what
I am trying to create to the people who already
get the why in hopes of finding the people
to cocreate the how.
The WHY should be obvious if I have to explain
to you how our current system is broken you
probably just aren't my people yet, and that's
OK.
But if you believe capitalism is inherently
broken that it is designed to fail and it
needs to be dismantled, peacefully, then you
are who I am looking for.
The how is complex and I have spent the last
few years specifically diving deeper into
that it involves unleashing our collective
power through technology the power of the
crowd our own individual passions and an overall
shift from a system based on competition to
one based on cooperation.
there is not enough time to explain all of
the ins and outs but that is about the jist
of what I can do in that amount of time
now to explain the what to the best of my
ability.
This is not so easy for me.
The best name I have been able to come up
with is Technological socialism.
We start with one project which soon becomes
the core of a massive global cooperative that
owns everything.
We start one project and it devours capitalism
from inside.
We create a global cooperative that will eventually
own nearly everything.
We start with technology because it is cheap
and has infinite potential but we do move
on to the entire means of production.
When it makes sense for us to own factories
and mines we buy factories and mines.
We create an online space that is designed
for collaboration.
Once that space is in existence we are then
able to create other technology from that.
Once we create the space for us to collaborate
on projects it unleashes our own human potential
because we are able to find projects that
speak to us and contribute in a way that is
meaningful to us and creating that platform
is easy that is not what is complex.
If we had Facebook that was designed for collaboration
and contribution instead of for profit and
we all owned it and it was run through democracy
and transparency think about what we could
do.
And that is what I am trying to create.
I need people who want to co create a world
where we have zero poverty where climate change
and other environmental catastrophes are a
priority we don't just gloss over in the name
of economics.
I just need those people so if you could please
share this video I need to find the people
who want to co create that world people who
want to put their time and energy into creating
a system based on cooperation in hopes of
creating a better world.
Not in hopes I can see the path I can see
it very clearly I just can’t explain it
all in a 5 minute video.
so if this spoke to you at all please contact
me become part of it.
If you just want to stay up to date on what
is going on I am hoping to well I am not hoping
this is going to happen I am going to do this
every day until it gets made so if you want
to follow that along and my own personal journey
then join my Facebook group on Crowd Democracy
I will keep that up to date if you want to
be involved and actually put your blood sweat
and tears like I'm going to into this please
contact me at my email and introduce yourself.
My email is collaborativedemocracy@gmail.com
Together we can come up with a better name
later but those are just what I have to work
with today.
So happy Birthday to me please share this
video and please contact me so we can co create
a better system together.